<sburb>
    <classes>
<action class='damaraTalk1' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Talk to Damara.'>
      <args>
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: sooooo
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: megido
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: here we are again
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: i guess
      @damara_squint DAMARA: 
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: please tell me this reunion is as awkward for you as it is for me
      @damara_squint DAMARA: 
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: not gonna say nofin huh
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: just going to stand there and leave me wrigglin on the hook during this frosty silence
      @meenah_angrytalk MEENAH: come on you nutty bitch at least do SOM-EFIN to break the ice
      @damara_fu3 DAMARA: 
      @meenah_happier MEENAH: T)(ANK you
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: hey you didnt by any chance kidnap nitrams lusus did you
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: or steal all his dorky fiduspawn loot
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: i thought we were past this
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: dont tell me youre still tormenting the guy even after eternity
      @damara_talk DAMARA: あなたのデュアルフォークを取る。二回自分自身をファック。
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: do what to myself twice with my double W)(AT exactly??
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: cod damn your weird accent is thick as ever
      @damara_talk DAMARA: あなたに性的快感を与えるために十分な厚さではない。
      @damara_squinttalk DAMARA: あなたはあなたの言葉で私を退屈続けるのだろうか？または。あなたは私の服を脱ぐのだろうか？
      @damara_smilemeantalk DAMARA: 私はあなたの歯の間に私の乳首を感じるようにしたい。
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: wha
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: did you just tell me to bite something or
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: screw it i give up
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: language barrier be a fuckin motherglubber
      @damara_smoke DAMARA: 
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action class='damaraTalk2' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Ask Damara to join.'>
      <args>
      @meenah_happier MEENAH: hey so guess what! im building an army to kill lord ahahahaha
      @meenah_creepylaugh:#aka#sea-lol MEENAH: S)(-ELL O)( S)(-ELL
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: like you could give a fuck about saving reality and or wouldnt just be a huge backstabbin liability out there
      @damara_idle DAMARA: 十分に公平。
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: but just for shits an cuttles uh
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: been sorta wondering
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: back when we like
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: kind of ruined each others shit
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: because of that whole cycle of revenge deal
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: and i ended up dyin and god tiering and all
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: remember that
      @damara_smilemean DAMARA: 私が覚えている。
      @damara_smiletalk DAMARA: 時々私は、そのメモリに自慰行為。
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: aight not sure i followed that but ill assume it was more weird skanky sass
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: but what i want to know is
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: after the fight
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: did i hurt you bad enough that you maybe
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: crawled off and died somewhere
      @meenah_wink MEENAH: like in a quest cocoon
      @damara_idle DAMARA: ...
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: were you maybe all bloodied up from all those forkins
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: and then maybe along comes a friend with a maddening inability to hold a grudge against you for the ways you fucked him over
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: maybe trotting along in his new robo horse body and swooped your bloody torso up on his back
      @meenah_creepytalk MEENAH: galloped off to your cocoon and draped you on the slab while probly not havin the nerve to finish you off
      @meenah_creepylaugh:#like-the-ones-in-your-batty-as-fuck-goddamn-belfry? MEENAH: this ringin any bells
      @damara_huhtalk DAMARA: 性交あなたは何を話している？白痴雌犬。
      @meenah_angrytalk MEENAH: IM AXING IF YOU AR-E A GOD TI-ER YOU INSCRUTABL-E FIS)(WIF-E
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: holy mackerel gettin info outta yous like prying a pearl from a slutty murderous clam
      @damara_squinttalk DAMARA: ハマグリは、真珠を生成しません。あなたは海の何も知らない。
      @meenah_angrytalk MEENAH: yeah i know clams dont make pearls!!! look i just misspoke it was a hasty burn ok
      @meenah_angrytalk MEENAH: dont be calling out my authority on the ocean dmeg you know i got all watery junk on LOCK 
      @meenah_fishtalk MEENAH: who you think you tryin to rile up with that amateur noise
      @damara_smoke DAMARA: あなたは非常に怒っているように見える。性交をチルアウト。のはお互いに触れてみましょう。私と一緒に投石入手してください。
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: omg i cant understand you
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: chill out and do W)(AT with you...
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: going to ask again as simple as i can
      @meenah_angrytalk MEENAH: M-EGIDO AR-E YOU A MAGIC IMMORTAL TIM-E FAIRYWITC)( WIT)( S-ECR-ET BUTT-ERFLY WINGS: Y-ES OR NO
      @damara_talk DAMARA: 正確にどのくらいの。あなたは知りたいですか？水のビッチ。
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: damara
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: if horrible conversations was a video game you would truly be last boss
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: now where the fucks aranea and her lil windbag stand lets just get this jam over with already
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>


<action class='damaraTalk3' sprite='meenah' command='talk' name='Be Damara.'>
      <args>
      @damara_talk DAMARA: あなたは私になりたいですか？
      @damara_talk DAMARA: あなたは私にはできません。あなたは私を理解できない場合。
      @damara_talk DAMARA: さらに。あなたは私にはできません。あなたは私を性交することができない場合。
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: ummm yeah no idea what you said
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: guess someone who speaks your gibberish needs to ask
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action class='damaraTalk4' sprite='rufioh' command='talk' name='Talk to Damara.'>
      <args>
      @rufioh_offendedtalk \nRUFIOH: hey doll... don't suppose you had anyth1ng to do w1th the recent d1sappearance of my lusus, d1d you?
      @damara_talk DAMARA: もちろんそんなことはない。あなたの告発は言語道断。 
      @rufioh_offended \nRUFIOH: yeah... sure... l1ke 1 bel1eve that!
      @rufioh_talk \nRUFIOH: l1ke 1'm not so on to your tr1cks by now...
      @damara_huhtalk DAMARA: 黙れ。そう。あなたはまだ彼と別れたのですか？
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: no... not yet...
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: 1 tr1ed... but 1 just couldn't do 1t... 1t's hard, you know?
      @damara_meantalk DAMARA: あなたは、どういう意味ですか。それは恋人があなたを裏切ったときに感じる？はい、私は知っている。
      @rufioh_sadtalk \nRUFIOH: d*mn... so cold, g1rl. why can't you let the past go?
      @rufioh_offended \nRUFIOH: anyway... once 1 actually do get up the nerve to break 1t to h1m... don't be th1nk1ng th1s 1s your b1g chance w1th me!
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: 1t's over between us for good... k1nda for obv1ous reasons... so just fr1ends, you d1g?
      @damara_fiendish DAMARA: 右。我々が表示されます。
      @rufioh_happytalk \nRUFIOH: haha... yeah, 1 f1gured you'd be l1ke that. 
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: anyway, meenah k1nd of needs to keep go1ng through th1s bubble... 1 know you l1ke to make sh*t d1ff1cult for everyone all the t1me, but...
      @rufioh_surprisetalk \nRUFIOH: you th1nk you could get r1d of that b1g *ss 1ceberg th1ng you dropped there?
      @damara_idle DAMARA: いいえクソ方法。
      @rufioh_sheepish \nRUFIOH: aw, come on... do 1t for me, damara?
      @damara_smilemeantalk DAMARA:罰金。しかし、あなたは私に借りがある。性的な接待。
      @rufioh_laugh \nRUFIOH: hahahaha... wow... alr1ght uh... maybe? just go...
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action class='damaraTalk5' sprite='horuss' command='talk' name='Talk to Damara.'>
      <args>
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Oh, hello Damara. I heard you were having a mechanical issue with your chest over here. Mind if I take a 100k?
      @damara_talk DAMARA: あなたは私の胸をいつでも表示することができます。
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; I... think you said yes? Sorry, I really struggle with your coarse lowb100d accent.
      @damara_talk DAMARA: 私のおっぱいの上にミルクを注いでください。
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; I didn't quite understand that either. Something about milk? Served to you in a particular way?
      @horuss_hmmtalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Yes, if you would like some milk, I can bring you some later. I'll just need to equip my steam powered deSTRENGTHening gloves so that I may hand you the glass without shattering it.
      @damara_talk DAMARA: ない。手袋を着用しないでください。私はそれがラフ好きです。私の体を押しつぶす。馬男。
      @horuss_hmmtalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; I really need to finish my universal translation device so we can have a more coherent conversation. It's just so difficult to get the circuitry to function correctly when one insists on relying on steam power.
      @damara_squinttalk DAMARA: あなたは、幽霊のような私の性器が性的クライマックスを持っていることを確認してください。あなたの幻の馬のペニスでそれを行う必要があります。
      @horuss_smiletalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; You want me to bring your what to what e%25actly with my what?
      @damara_smiletalk DAMARA: 私の裸の底にあなたの汗まみれの顔をこする。
      @horuss_idle HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Hmm. I...
      @horuss_sweat_bashful HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Sure?
      @damara_smilemeantalk DAMARA: 私はあなたのアジアの女子高生です。ズタズタに私の服を減らすことができます。あなたは私を喜ばせる必要があります。あなたのホーンを使用してください。
      @horuss_sweat_grin HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Do what with your schoolgirl uniform?
      @horuss_sweat_talk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; I wouldn't want to do anything to ruin it. It's quite nice. 
      @horuss_hmmtalk HORUSS: 8=D &lt; But perhaps I could craft a robotic avatar for you, emulating your fashion choices. Actually, if I did that, I could install more sensible speech algorithms, so that I could understand you for a change.
      @damara_mean DAMARA: 静かにしています。黙って私をファック。
      @horuss_sweat_idle HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Um. *Cough.*
      @damara_meantalk DAMARA: 私の体内に入る。または。私はあなたを破壊するだろう。
      @horuss_sweat_bashful HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Damara, forgive me if I'm leaping to conclusions, but has the nature of your cryptic remarks been leaning... well...
      @horuss_oops HORUSS: 8=D &lt; A little b100?
      @damara_lewd DAMARA: 
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action class='damaraTalk6' sprite='horuss' command='talk' name='Be Damara.'>
      <args>
      @damara_talk DAMARA: あなたは私になりたいですか？
      @damara_talk DAMARA: あなたは私にはできません。あなたは私を理解できない場合。
      @damara_talk DAMARA: さらに。あなたは私にはできません。あなたは私を性交することができない場合。
      @horuss_sweat_grin HORUSS: 8=D &lt; Come again?
      @horuss_sweat_grin HORUSS: 8=D &lt; I suppose Rufioh should ask. He's always been the only one who can parse your vulgar, peasant tongue.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>
  	</classes>
</sburb>