<sburb>
    <classes>
<action sprite='meenah' class='expoTalk1' command='talk' name='Status report.'>
      <args>
      @meenah_annoyed:#kelp MEENAH: welp
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: im a total failure
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: didnt recruit a single ghost for my army
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: except for one guy but he was asleep
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: Don't lose hope! I know our group of friends is a 8it lackluster in the motivation department, 8ut there are plenty of other souls out there.
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: You just need to find someone with the right amount of moxy to get you started. Then I'm sure more will follow.
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: Who knows, if you keep exploring, may8e someone like that will 8e right around the corner!
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: you seem more psyched about my army plan than you did before
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: whats with the change of tuna
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: I've started to 8elieve that what you're doing may 8e important. Just a feeling.
      @aranea_happytalk:#Or,-prongs-of-a-fork,-if-you-will. ARANEA: It could 8e every 8it as critical as my quest to find the cheru8. I think it all could 8e related. Like legs of a stool that won't stand unless all are in place.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: how is cherubquest goin btw
      @aranea_think ARANEA: Uh... ok.
      @aranea_think ARANEA: I've still 8een........ a little preoccupied.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: girl please
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: you been draggin your talking booth around to hassle people with facts aintcha
      @aranea_surprised ARANEA: This is my last session, I swear!!!!!!!!
      @aranea_talk ARANEA: After this, I promised myself I would retire the exposition stand for good. May8e I'll put it up for sale, and try to recoup some of the su8stantial losses required to operate it.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: aranea we are such failures at stuff together
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: why are we such a couple of gorgeous and sexy failures at things
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: I don't know, 8ut we can't give up!
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: Once I close down shop here, I will redou8le my efforts to find that cheru8.
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: The first thing to do will 8e to figure out her name. It's 8een so maddeningly elusive, almost as if someone's taken care to scru8 any reference to it throughout paradox space, whether in memories or reality.
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: ok then how about this
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: while im out there fishin for recruits ill keep an ear out for clues about her
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: and while youre out there cherub hunting maybe you can see if anyone wants to serve the lil condesce in her slammin new imperial army
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: itll be
      @meenah_happy MEENAH: teamfork
      @aranea_happier ARANEA: That sounds like a great plan!
      @aranea_happier ARANEA: Now let's hurry this up so we can get started on that. What would you like me to tell you a8out in exchange for the precious few 8oon8ucks I have left?
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>


<action sprite='meenah' class='expoTalk2' command='talk' name='Tell me about Rufioh Nitram.'>
      <args>
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: The Rogue of 8reath was always a very popular mem8er of our group. Pro8a8ly the most popular, I'd say. Sort of the anti-me, in that respect. Ever the recipient of romantic solicitations whichever way he turned. Sort of the anti-Cronus, in that respect.
      @meenah_creepylaugh MEENAH: aw yeah sick ampora burn outta nowhere hi 5
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: Indeed. His mutation made him an outcast, though. To avoid the unwanted attention his wings would 8ring him, he took refuge in the forest among those who welcomed his differences, and learned their ways.
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: The Lost Weea8oos was a guild of youthful tree-dwelling troll otakus with a zeal for fisticuffs, flight, and various forms of exotic eastern theater. 8ane to the enemies of hijinks, scourge to the seafaring classes who...
      @meenah_fish MEENAH: NOP-E
      @meenah_fishtalk MEENAH: NOT LISFININ TO T)(IS LA LA LA GLUB GLUB GLUB
      @aranea_annoyedtalk ARANEA: #77003c (GLUB GLUB GLUB GLUB)## centuries of feuding with the Kemonomimi tri8es #77003c (GLUB GLUB GLUB LA LA LA LA GLUB GLUB GLUB)## ceremonial torchlight yaoi festivals #77003c (LA LA LA LA GLUB GLUB LA LA LA)## tsundere quadrant vacillation #77003c (GLUUUUUB GLUBGLUBGLUBGLUB GLUUUUUUUUUB)## threw down a daggerlance to challenge the guild's high seme for dominance #77003c (NO NO NO NO NO NO NO NO NO NO)## ultimately served like a shonen on Shitsuji Island.
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: hey serket
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: how much i gotta pay you to zip yer blowhole on this shit so tight you never bring it up again
      @aranea_happier ARANEA: For such a service, I will require nothing short of the large gold statue in your palace. I think you know which one I'm talking a8out.
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: you drive a hard bargain serks
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: but you got a deal
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>


<action sprite='meenah' class='expoTalk3' command='talk' name='Tell me about Horuss Zahhak.'>
      <args>
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: The Page of Void was a self taught master of mechanics, an avid patron of the fine arts, a passionate 8ody 8uilder, archer, am8rosia collector and steamwright. A poet, a scholar, a warrior, a lover, he was all that his caste demanded and more. A true troll Renaissance man. His name means "He Who Stalks With The Muscle8easts."
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: 8ut all of his proficiencies were hard won, 8uilt from the 8lank slate as his aspect would imply, advancing at the slow pace his class would as well. Yet in spite of all he worked to make something of himself, he amounted to very little. Responsi8le for neither great feats of heroism nor acts of villainy, he was just another game piece to 8e moved a8out the 8oard. The aspect ruling his life would always conspire to dampen his relevance.
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: Void is easily the most mysterious aspect, the one which inherently defies rational understanding. This makes it particularly fascinating, and just as frustrating, to light players such as myself. Casting illumination upon nothing itself is futile. For to truly know void is to paradoxically cause it not to 8e!
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: The role of the void player is to somehow em8race nothingness, to 8ecome one with it. And yet in total contradiction with this, to make use of the power it grants and serve a role of relevance, one must find a way to overcome it! To see the limitless potential in the void. To find everything within nothing, and 8ring it into 8eing. 
      @aranea_annoyed #77003c MEENAH: zzzzzzzzzzz##
      @aranea_angrytalk ARANEA: Hey!!!!!!!!
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: wuh
      @aranea_annoyedtalk ARANEA: This is a perfect case in point, regarding the path of the void player. So resistant is his story to having a relevant 8earing on anything, you fell asleep and didnt hear a word.
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: yeah thats nice
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: WH-ER-E MA MON-EY
      @aranea_facepalmtalk ARANEA: You don't get any. Your slum8er voided the transaction.
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: dag
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>


<action sprite='meenah' class='expoTalk4' command='talk' name='Tell me about Damara Megido.'>
      <args>
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: The Witch of Time was not always the party's 8iggest trou8lemaker. If you recall, you wore that tiara for a long time. ::::)
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: yeah yeah
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: Once she was as meek as can 8e. Hailing from the eastern provinces, she migrated across the seas and settled near the forest concealing Rufioh's guild. The two of them 8ecame quite fond of each other, and shared many interests!
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: He secretly 8egan seeing someone else, 8elieving she knew nothing. 8ut she always suspected his infidelity, and over time grew quite distraught. 8ut her sadness never quite turned to rage and malevolence. Not until you... involved yourself. 
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: ugh do we really have to go through this
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: If you'd like to earn your money, then yes!
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: bleh fine
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: After we 8egan our game, you quickly determined that winning was going to 8e an uphill 8attle with our team. Everyone was so preoccupied with their interpersonal issues, and no one seemed in any shape to 8e fighting major 8attles. Sound familiar?
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: deja vus a bitch serk
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: So you did your 8est to rile up the crew any way you could. Appealing to peoples insecurities, 8uried hostilities, 8rewing rivalries... needling anyone you could into confrontation with others. Your theory was that increasing everyone's state of aggression would make them 8etter equipped to play the game. And you were sort of right a8out that! 8ut the Alternians would prove it. Not our group, sadly.
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: The poor girl who took the 8runt of your 8ullying tactics was Damara Megido. You talked up her matesprit's 8etrayal making her feel even more dreadful, while pushing him further into the arms of her rival, until she simply snapped. She attacked him, paralyzing him from the neck down. You finally got the aggressive confrontation you were looking for. Unfortunately, you unleashed something even you weren't prepared for, and you had to deal with her yourself. After a long 8loody duel, she killed you. And you would have stayed dead if not for me!
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: You never listened to me. You just kept needling and fussing and meddling until eventually you paid the price, and I had to 8ail you out.
      @meenah_wut2 MEENAH: (arg how bad do i even want this stupid money...)
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: Damara has 8een unhinged ever since. 8y increasing her violent tendencies, instead of 8eing an asset in the game, she 8ecame a loose canon, ar8itrarily showing up at key moments throughout the timeline to sa8otage us. 
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: So radical was her shift in personality, I've had a hard time 8elieving your incitement was solely to 8lame. It always seemed like other forces were in play, as if her acts, though apparently haphazard, were in keeping with some inscruta8le agenda. Of course it doesn't help that it's so hard to understand her even on a good day.
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: Strangely, the only time she was eager to help us was when we were preparing to initiate the Scratch. And it's a good thing she was, since I'm not sure anyone else would have had the a8ility to do that kind of damage to the Cardinal Movement and release its energy. 
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: It was almost a little eerie how happily she complied with our plan. What did Rufioh say she said? Something a8out how we would all finally get what we deserved...
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: Which at the time, I thought sounded chilling. 8ut there's really two ways of looking at it. One is how the Scratch re8ooted our world into a state of pure chaos, culminating in the annihilation of our universe. 8ut on the other hand, we all got the chance to live out our wildest fantasies as adults on Alternia! 
      @aranea_happytalk ARANEA: At least you and I sure did. And I wouldn't dou8t she feels the same way.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: so
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: we done?
      @aranea_happier ARANEA: That's it!
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: toughest 5 bucks i ever made
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk1' command='talk' name='SAY WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?'>
      <args>
      @! Damara!!! What the hell are you doing this deep into the game! Good grief, you are such a teen delinquent. I never should have let you out of Doc Scratch's pervert chamber in the alternate universe.
      @damara_smilemeantalk DAMAR#000000 WHOOPS, nooooooooo no no no.##
      @! I'm not gonna let you respond. You're just going say something totally filthy in Japanese again and make everyone uncomfortable.
      @damara_lewd #000000 WHOA CUT THAT OUT!##
      @! Sheesh. I guess this is what happens when you don't have a proper upbringing by a decent guardian. Or at least one who isn't a four foot tall asshole in suspenders, who's kind of like a creepy puppet uncle.
      @! Look, let's all just chill out here. No more lewd Asian shenanigans, got it?? You may notice I bought a new franchise recently.
      @! Cost me a fortune! I had to pawn a ring that used to belong to some dirtbag just to make the down payment.
      @! But I should be able to recoup the losses, if I just tweak the business model a little. Hear me out. Instead of giving people money to listen to my shit? I think I might actually start CHARGING people for the service. Crazy, I know, right?
      @! I've been thinking of dividing up my offers into a series of handsomely priced explanation bundles called EXPOSITION PAKS where I would...
      @damara_fu3 DAMARA:
      @! Oh kaaay, guess you're not down with that? 
      @! What would you pay for an explanation? Want to make an offer?
      @! Yeah you're not gonna pay me a goddamn penny, are you.
      @damara_smoke DAMARA:
      @! Ok fine. I'll give you these explanations for free. Let's call it a loss leader. You'll tell your friends, maybe they'll tell their friends, then the dead presidents start rolling in.
      @! Yes? Yes???
      @damara_huh DAMARA:
      @! Aw fuck it. Just tell me what you wanna know.
      @! But just a heads up, these stories are gonna be pretty shitty! I ain't no light player.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk2' command='talk' name='Hey, before we start...'>
      <args>
      @! Did you get here with Damara before you got here with Meenah? If you did I think I'm going to flip my shit. That is one cracked way of going through this game. Stop talking to me right now and go come back as Meenah.
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk3' command='talk' name='Tell me about Damara Megido.'>
      <args>
      @! You want me to tell you about YOU??? Talk about self absorbed, but alright.
      @! You say stuff in Japanese, and when people who actually speak Japanese read it they probably laugh because the Japanese is so shitty. Sorry to burst your bubble Damara but the things you say started out in English, went through the google translator, and then out again so that it vaguely makes sense when translated back to English. So you aren't really authentic troll Japanese, you're fake troll Japanese.
      @damara_fu2 DAMARA:
      @! Whoa don't kill the messenger! Relax. Everyone thinks you're great. In fact, there's probably someone out there RIGHT NOW drawing some weird porn of you.
      @damara_huh DAMARA: ???
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk4' command='talk' name='Tell me about Mituna Captor.'>
      <args>
      @! Mega Man Sollux has some problems. He falls down and stuff and talks on a 4chan background, because of 4chan. But in spite of that, he's brave and does his best and everyone loves him. Also no one can read a damn thing he says. His quirk is the least legible of all quirks, with Damara's coming in at a close second.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk5' command='talk' name='Tell me about Rufioh Nitram.'>
      <args>
      @! With apologies to Dante Basco. Dante, I'm sorry about this. All of this. I am so, so sorry. You were leading the regular, modest life of a Hollywood superstar, then this shit happened. Everything is broken forever. I liked your work in The Last Airbender. You know what's funny is how there are probably some people who are reading this right now who have no idea what the fuck I'm talking about. But you know what? What the FUCK else is even new.
      @! Anyway. Bangarang, dude.
      @!:#rufiozuko.tumblr.com Bangarang.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk6' command='talk' name='Tell me about Kankri Vantas.'>
      <args>
      @! Did you know: it is a Homestuck fact that 99 percent of all readers didn't read or care about anything Kankri said. So in other words, he is exactly like all terrible social justice bloggers. Some social justice bloggers get angry at the joke that he is, but those are the terrible ones, and being terrible is why they get angry. They want to be terrible in peace without being mocked. That is what it is like to be a justified target of ridicule. You feel sad and angry all the time and you don't know why. 
      @! Kankri wears a cute red sweater and is otherwise fairly adorable. Porrim acts like his mom which is also cute as hell.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>
  
<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk7' command='talk' name='Tell me about Meulin Leijon.'>
      <args>
      @! Meulin is the deaf Nepeta in this kickass smorgasbord of disabled characters. She speaks in ASL to say memes which are called mimes because it's one letter away and therefore a play on words. But you can't actually use ASL to say animated tumblr gifs, you can only say words. She otherwise reads lips, which is funny because her bff sewed his damn mouth shut so they just sign memes to each other all day while stoned. It is implied that they smoke catnip together, as if it were marijuana, which is an especially amusing notion to people who like drugs. Moving on??
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk8' command='talk' name='Tell me about Latula Pyrope.'>
      <args>
      @! Latula is the gamegrl to Mituna's gamebro. Gamebros and gamegrls aren't really "types of people" so much as they are hollow cliches which are patronizing to multiple groups of people on multiple levels. So in other words, perfect attributes for some 1.5 dimensional NPC-caliber characters stocking a fun jrpg style walkaround game. Wait what was I talking about? Oh yeah Latula.
      @! Latula's so rad but she can't smell. I think I agree with Karkat, that's not a disability. That's just like having a cold all the time, but without any actual symptoms or problems. Who cares. Latula likes to high five people all the time, but doesn't like to be left hanging. That's a pun, because Redglare liked to hang people with nooses. Mindfang ultimately left Redglare hanging that way too. I'm explaining jokes here. What? I told you these stories would suck. You get what you pay for.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk9' command='talk' name='Tell me about Porrim Maryam.'>
      <args>
      @! Porrim is better at social justice than Kankri because she isn't a boring asshole. Some social justice people should try looking into that. Porrim wants there to be equality for ladies. Not everybody cares about that though, which makes it hard for people like Porrim. That's the way it is in the real world. CHALLENGES. But in any case, she is a vampire with cool tattoos. End of story.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk10' command='talk' name='Tell me about Aranea Serket.'>
      <args>
      @! Aranea is a blabbermouth, just like Mindfang. She says long things both as a teen and as a sexy pirate adult that make people ask what am I even reading? It's about time I took over this exposition stand. The way I describe shit is a million times better. She sure charged me enough for it. God I took a bath on this thing. Why was it so expensive??? IT'S MADE OF FUCKING CARDBOARD.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk11' command='talk' name='Tell me about Horrus Zahhak.'>
      <args>
      @! This dude is just Equius on horse steroids. The end.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk12' command='talk' name='Tell me about Kurloz Makara.'>
      <args>
      @! He chewed off his tongue and sewed his mouth shut because he's a weirdo in cahoots with Gamzee and English. Who even knows what they're up to. It's probably just a lot of stupid bullshit. Meaningless, clownish nonsense. Want to know why they're assembling the wicked ensemble? They probably just think it's funny. Kurloz speaks in bones when he does his clown hypnosis shit but otherwise he mimes everything because get this: he's pretty much literally a mime. Also a juggalo. Because that's exactly what Homestuck needed. Another fucking juggalo. Homestuck needed another juggalo like it needed... 
      @! Well, another twelve trolls I guess. 
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk13' command='talk' name='Tell me about Cronus Ampora.'>
      <args>
      @! Cronus is the worst character in Homestuck by a nautical mile. Any questions?
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

<action sprite='damara' class='expo2Talk14' command='talk' name='Tell me about Meenah Peixes.'>
      <args>
      @! Meenah is kind of throwing a bone to the pisces people who got stuck with Feferi. Feferi didn't really do anything and then she died. Meenah is a cool sassy punk who has more important stuff to do than Feferi ever did. You just spent like the last three hours playing through these games from her POV so obviously you know that. You're probably sick of fish puns by now. After a while you start running out of fish puns. You can overdo it with fish puns, much like you can overfish the ocean. You start literally running out of fucking fish. Be careful out there.
      @! Meenah discovered that raising and army is hard. But you know what's really hard? What's really hard is making games. Games disguise the effort that go into them probably like few other crafts. In order to make a game that is even slightly better than mediocre, someone probably had to die in the process. Like building pyramids. Nobody actually died while making these games though, hence they were just ok. But still if you add up all the work done collectively on these last three games, it probably was comparable to the manhours that went into [S] Cascade. You know what that is? That's a silly ass fact.
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>


  	</classes>
</sburb>