<sburb>
<classes>
<action class='andrewTalk1' command='talk' name='This guy again?'>
      <args>
      @! Oh. It's you. Scram kid!
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: hey orange dude
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: tell me your deal already
      @!:#Do.-Not.-Fuck-with-me. I said get lost Feferi!!!!
      @meenah_fish MEENAH: whoferi???
      @! Alright. I see what's going on here. You clearly have developed feelings for me. I understand. I led you on.
      @! Remember when I said bring me a horse and I am yours forever?
      @! Total lie!
      @! Sorry, but my heart is still set on Vriska. She will be my wife.
      @meenah_idle MEENAH: whos vriska
      @! That girl over there. No, don't look! Shhhhhhhhhh. Let's try to keep it down, ok? You're going to ruin this for me.
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: her??
      @meenah_wut MEENAH: dog aint she a little young for you
      @! No, but that's the thing! She's spent like however many years being a ghost, so she's older now! That means it's not creepy.
      @! Who even knows how many years she spent here? Maybe 100??? Hell, she might even be older than me now! See? Totally not creepy anymore. Case closed!
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: i dont know what yer talkin about but you sound like an asshole
      @! Just need to find the right moment to make my move. Only problem is, I lost the ring.
      @! John FUCKING Egbert has it. Doesn't look like he's gonna let it go either, the bastard. 
      @! Gotta make a plan. Think, imagination, think. Argh, the one time I really need you!
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: yo i got boatloads a bling
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: i could sell you a ring
      @! You could??? Oh man, perfect. How much?
      @meenah_happy~dialogimg_ks MEENAH: 
      @! ARE YOU FUCKING SERIOUS.
      @! What makes you think I've got that kind of dough just lying around?!
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: thats my price pumpkin skin you want the ring or not
      @! Alright. Fine. Guess I've got no choice but to pony up.
      @! Just... don't tell anyone, ok? I kind of promised I would use this money for something else.
      @meenah_annoyedtalk MEENAH: none ma biz homes deal or no deal
      @! Yeah. Here.
      @meenah_happytalk MEENAH: awwwww yeah check them mad staxx
      @meenah_creepylaugh MEENAH: here you go loverboy
      @! Thanks!
      @! Wait...
      @! Is this ring...
      @! Did you steal this...
      @! From Cronus?
      @meenah_wink MEENAH: fo sho
      @! ...
      @! Ew.
      @meenah_angrytalk MEENAH: NO R-EFUNDS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
      @! :(
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

</classes>
</sburb>