<sburb>
<classes>
<action class='kanayaTalk1' sprite='rose' command='talk' name='Talk to Kanaya.'>
      <args>
      @rose_concern ROSE: Not to harp on the issue, but,
      @rose_concern ROSE: Now that you can switch on and off, so to speak, how often do you think you'll resort to phosphorescence?
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: I Dont Know
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: What Do You Think
      @rose_talk ROSE: Well, which state is more comfortable?
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: I Could Go Either Way
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Ill Probably Switch On If Im Walking Through A Dark Corridor
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Now That I Think About It
      @kanaya2_smirktalk KANAYA: Its Been A Long Time Since I Could Even Be In The Dark
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Maybe Ill Leave It Off For A While And Refamiliarize Myself With The Experience Of Nonillumination
      @rose_idle ROSE: Makes sense.
      @rose_talk ROSE: Was this a biological feature common to other trolls?
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: Um
      @rose_talk ROSE: I'm sorry. I'm really pestering you about this, aren't I?
      @rose_talk ROSE: We've never talked about it. I guess I was trying to be polite, but I've been really curious about it.
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: No Thats Ok
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Im Told Its A Trait Confined To Those Of My Caste
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: They Tended To Spend A Lot Of Time In The Brooding Caverns Where A Convenient Source Of Light Was Often Handy
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: That Part Of It Makes Sense To Me But I Have No Idea What The Evolutionary Purpose Was For The Sort Of Thirst Which Accompanies This Perk
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Strikes Me As An Odd Liability But What Do I Know
      @rose_concern ROSE: Maybe to frighten predators away from innocent grubs?
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: Maybe
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Or Perhaps It Was A Measured Defect Imposed On Us
      @kanaya2_bored KANAYA: To Keep The Auxiliatrices On A Short Leash
      @rose_talk ROSE: I'll agree with that assessment, on the grounds that I've always been a sucker for a good conspiracy theory.
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: The Condition Was Often Glamorized In Certain Works Of Literature
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: But Theres Really Nothing That Great About It
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Not Nearly As Useful As Other Abilities Like The Psychic Gifts Which Some Lowbloods Are Predisposed To
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Though I Guess Its Pretty Useful If You Want To Keep The Plans You Made After Someone Punches A Hole Through Your Gut
      @rose_talk ROSE: I can see how that could present a whole world of convenience.
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: Speaking of plans, doing anything later?
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: Not Really
      @rose_happytalk ROSE: I'm working on some stuff right now, but later, maybe once you're finished escorting your guest around, would you like to do something?
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: Sure
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: Anything In Particular That You Have In Mind
      @rose_talk ROSE: Not really. Just to hang out. If you're up for it!
      @kanaya2_happytalk KANAYA: Yeah That Sounds Okay
      @meenah_annoyed MEENAH: (holy mackerel get a fuckin room)
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>
<action class='kanayaTalk2' sprite='dave' command='talk' name='Talk to Kanaya.'>
      <args>
      @dave_talk DAVE: (you shattered the ring but theres more cracks in your rap)
      @dave_talk DAVE: (ima top off your glass cause devastations on tap)
      @dave_huh DAVE: (wait no)
      @dave_talk DAVE: (your act couldnt suck more dick with a puppet in your lap)
      @dave_huh DAVE: (what)
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: (puppet... man where that come from)
      @dave_talk DAVE: (you shattered the ring but theres more cracks in your rap)
      @dave_talk DAVE: (your flows like warm milk that goes good with a nap)
      @dave_smug DAVE: (haha yes)
      @dave_talk DAVE: (shit lets be rails ill be the shoosh to your pap)
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: (wait that makes no fuckin sense)
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: (naw ill stick with the milk one)
      @dave_talk DAVE: (yall claimin to be the lord of time)
      @dave_talk DAVE: (all ya makin me feel is bored with your rhymes)
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: (thats ok i guess)
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: (still feel like i should work puppets into this)
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: (no idea why)
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: (what rhymes with puppets)
      @dave_idle DAVE: (uh)
      @dave_huh DAVE: (smuppets)
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: (dave no thats the same fuckin thing)
      @dave_idle DAVE: (muppets)
      @dave_huh DAVE: (what the fuck)
      @dave_huh DAVE: (the only thing that rhymes with puppets is different kinds of puppets!!!)
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: ...
      @dave_huh DAVE: whoa
      @dave_huh DAVE: hey uh
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: how much of that did you hear
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: By The Tenor Of The Question Ill Assume More Than You Would Prefer
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: all that shit was a work in progress
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: aint fit for hype yet
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: why you gotta be eavesdroppin
      @kanaya2_idle KANAYA: I Wasnt
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: I Was Just Standing Here And You Slowly Wandered Over In A Totally Oblivious Stupor
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: You Were Mumbling Your Rhymes And Walked Right Up To Me And Did Not Notice Me Until Now
      @dave_huh DAVE: shit
      @dave_huh DAVE: was i
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: sorry i guess i just got caught up in my raps
      @meenah_ohyes MEENAH: do more!
      @dave_huh DAVE: what
      @dave_huh DAVE: no
      @dave_huhtalk DAVE: i cant those rhymes are still too rough around the edges
      @meenah_creepy MEENAH: come on
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: no itll suck
      @dave_idle DAVE: i mean
      @dave_talk DAVE: i could freestyle a bit i guess
      @dave_talk DAVE: i dont know if i got a live performance in me now
      @dave_talk DAVE: maybe it could work if someone dropped a beat
      @dave_smug DAVE: need a good beat i could probably kill it with a fly beat
      @meenah_talk MEENAH: aheh hem...
      @meenah_fishtalk:#no-wait-wait... MEENAH: dum dum PS)( ba dum dum PS)(
      @meenah_fishtalk MEENAH: chum chum FIS)( ba chum chum FIS)(
      @dave_smug DAVE: awwwww yeah
      @dave_smug DAVE: that fish beat is the shizzle
      @dave_concern DAVE: thats what i am TALKING about
      @dave_madtalk DAVE: alright settle down motherfuckers here we go 
      @kanaya2_talk KANAYA: They Then Proceeded To Have One Of The Most Ambiguously Rated Rap Offs In The History Of Paradox Space While I Stood By And Regarded It Neutrally
      <!--  -->
      </args>
</action>

</classes>
</sburb>